to my stage show freedom of life and death
which premieres and less than a month
Stockholm is already sold out but tickets
still exists in Gothenburg Malmö Lund
Växjö Karlstad and Sundsvall the show is
Lord of the Flies from
1954 portrays a group of British
schoolboys decay into primitive barbarism
after they were stranded on an island with no adults
companion tell
illustrating How easily civilization goes
support calls in connection with becoming young
detained the segregation most often they have
after all, a lack of belonging is confirmed
that someone sees and hears them It is
of course perfectly fine with both
ultimately like Golding's Lord of the Flies
must be able to be reunited with responsibility
adults with the power to subdue barbarism
and that
reestablish civilized Ideal self